{
    "quiz": {
        "question": [
            {
                "id": 297,
                "_id": "12-01",
                "chapterId": 12,
                "question": "Specific information conveyed to a specific audience through an educational message is known as:",
                "refPage": "286",
                "possible0": "administration.",
                "possible1": "campaign theme.",
                "possible2": "technical content.",
                "possible3": "indirect considerations.",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 298,
                "_id": "12-02",
                "chapterId": 12,
                "question": "What type of campaign themes generally have high-quality materials ready for use in formats that include the Internet, posters, radio and television spots, and social media shares?",
                "refPage": "287",
                "possible0": "Pilot",
                "possible1": "Focus",
                "possible2": "Locally standardized",
                "possible3": "Nationally standardized",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 299,
                "_id": "12-03",
                "chapterId": 12,
                "question": "What does the Centers for Disease Control (CDC) refer to as the basic science of public health which allows an FLSE to target their goals and programs more effectively?",
                "refPage": "287",
                "possible0": "Nephrology",
                "possible1": "Epidemiology",
                "possible2": "Programming",
                "possible3": "Segmentation",
                "correctAnswer": 1,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 300,
                "_id": "12-04",
                "chapterId": 12,
                "question": "The FLSE needs to know and understand how literacy, language barriers, and special needs affect the:",
                "refPage": "287",
                "possible0": "target audience.",
                "possible1": "marketing forecast.",
                "possible2": "campaign protocols.",
                "possible3": "epidemiology of injury.",
                "correctAnswer": 0,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 301,
                "_id": "12-05",
                "chapterId": 12,
                "question": "What is referred to as the ability to read, write, speak, compute, and solve problems?",
                "refPage": "288",
                "possible0": "Legacy",
                "possible1": "Literacy",
                "possible2": "Experience",
                "possible3": "Demographics",
                "correctAnswer": 1,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 302,
                "_id": "12-06",
                "chapterId": 12,
                "question": "What describes the speaking, reading, and writing of English by people who learned another language before learning English?",
                "refPage": "289",
                "possible0": "English Literacy (EL)",
                "possible1": "Fundamentals of English (FOE)",
                "possible2": "Accessible English (AE)/Additional Accessible English (AAE)",
                "possible3": "English as a Second Language (ESL)/English as an Additional Language (EAL)",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 303,
                "_id": "12-07",
                "chapterId": 12,
                "question": "Braille, large print, audio, and/or accessible web content may make information more _____ for those with disabilities.",
                "refPage": "290",
                "possible0": "regulated",
                "possible1": "accessible",
                "possible2": "secondary",
                "possible3": "unaccessible",
                "correctAnswer": 1,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 304,
                "_id": "12-08",
                "chapterId": 12,
                "question": "The practice of using _____ when creating educational materials helps audiences understand material the first time they read or hear it.",
                "refPage": "290",
                "possible0": "statistics",
                "possible1": "large print",
                "possible2": "plain language",
                "possible3": "translation software",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 305,
                "_id": "12-09",
                "chapterId": 12,
                "question": "What type of marketing attempts to shift behavior to aid the consumer or society?",
                "refPage": "290",
                "possible0": "Social",
                "possible1": "Target",
                "possible2": "Producer",
                "possible3": "Commercial",
                "correctAnswer": 0,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 306,
                "_id": "12-10",
                "chapterId": 12,
                "question": "What is referred to as an overall approach to identifying and converting potential customers into actual customers?",
                "refPage": "291",
                "possible0": "Marketing plan",
                "possible1": "Marketing change",
                "possible2": "Marketing strategy",
                "possible3": "Marketing behavior",
                "correctAnswer": 2,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 307,
                "_id": "12-11",
                "chapterId": 12,
                "question": "What is an operational document that implements a strategy through specific activities at specific times?",
                "refPage": "291",
                "possible0": "Marketing plan",
                "possible1": "Target message",
                "possible2": "Promotional policy",
                "possible3": "Mutual aid agreement",
                "correctAnswer": 0,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 308,
                "_id": "12-12",
                "chapterId": 12,
                "question": "What are two high-visibility tools used by the FLSE Program Manager when developing a marketing strategy and plan to promote the organization’s products?",
                "refPage": "292",
                "possible0": "Safety tip sheets and change analysis",
                "possible1": "Marketing campaigns and proclamations",
                "possible2": "Accessibility principles and plain language",
                "possible3": "Audience segmentation and literacy concepts",
                "correctAnswer": 1,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 309,
                "_id": "12-13",
                "chapterId": 12,
                "question": "The FLSE Program Manager may need to collaborate with _____, as appropriate, who may already have relationships with local media.",
                "refPage": "292",
                "possible0": "a campaign manager",
                "possible1": "state printing facilities",
                "possible2": "regional safety officers",
                "possible3": "the organization’s Public Information Officer (PIO)",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 310,
                "_id": "12-14",
                "chapterId": 12,
                "question": "Newspapers, billboards, door hang tags, and online pages are examples of:",
                "refPage": "292",
                "possible0": "media resources.",
                "possible1": "advanced services.",
                "possible2": "risk reduction issues.",
                "possible3": "social marketing strategies.",
                "correctAnswer": 0,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 311,
                "_id": "12-15",
                "chapterId": 12,
                "question": "The FLSE Program Manager can mention how a smoke alarm, car safety seat, or personal flotation device could have prevented the incident:",
                "refPage": "293",
                "possible0": "openly to the public at any time.",
                "possible1": "when speaking with the media after an incident.",
                "possible2": "before all family members involved in the incident have been notified.",
                "possible3": "prior to distributing press releases online or through services such as PR Newswire.",
                "correctAnswer": 1,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            },
            {
                "id": 312,
                "_id": "12-16",
                "chapterId": 12,
                "question": "Faith-based organizations, cultural leaders, medical professionals, and community health workers can be powerful voices on behalf of fire and life safety educators as _____ forms of media.",
                "refPage": "294",
                "possible0": "redirecting",
                "possible1": "technological",
                "possible2": "noninfluencial",
                "possible3": "non-technological",
                "correctAnswer": 3,
                "isAnswered": 0,
                "isStudyDeckEnabled": 0
            }
        ]
    }
}
